Register to The Kay Swift Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Scripts, Outlines, Proposals, Notes, and Lyrics, Series II; 1.25' (3 boxes)
  - A CANDLE FOR ST. JUDE
    - Dialogue based on novel., 29 p. in various pagings; various sizes. (Box 12, Folder 376)
      Typescript, annotations in pencil.
      With: Suggestions (4 p.). Music (2 p.). Tabloid structure (13 p.). Notes from remarks by Rumer Godden (1 p.). 4 miscellaneous p.
    - Lyrics., 3 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 377)
  - CARNIVAL AT POOKER'S PEAK
    - Outline., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 378)
  - CENTURY 21
    - Script., 28 p.; 36 cm. (Box 12, Folder 379)
      With: notes for demonstration record (1 p.)
  - CIRCUS DAY [THE CIRCUS OF DR. LAO]
    - Outline., 7 p.; various sizes. (Box 12, Folder 380)
    - Notes., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 380)
    - Notes., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 380)
      Typescript, annotations in pencil and ink.
    - Notes., 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 381)
    - Notes., 7 p.; 32 cm. (Box 12, Folder 381)
    - Notes., 2 p.; 32 cm. (Box 12, Folder 381)
    - Notes., 3 p.; 32 cm. (Box 12, Folder 381)
    - Notes., 1 p.; 32 cm. (Box 12, Folder 381)
    - Lyrics., 1 leaf; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 382)
  - A CLOWN'S WORLD
    - Outline., 21 p., 19 p. [incomplete]; various sizes. (Box 12, Folder 383)
  - DANCERS IN THE DARK
    - Outline., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 384)
  - DEAR COOPERATOR
    - Outline., 4 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 385)
    - Outline., 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 385)
    - Outline., 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 385)
  - DR. RUSH PAYS A HOUSE-CALL / By Frederick Feirstein; with Alfred Stern, [3] p.; 28 cm.
  - FINE AND DANDY / by Donald Ogden Stewart; music by Kay Swift; lyrics by Paul James
    - Script., 147 p. in various pagings; 29 cm. (Box 13, Folder 387)
      Includes synopsis.
      With: 2 p. identifying typescript.
    - Script., 97 p. in various pagings; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 387)
    - Sides., 125 p. in various sizes; 36 cm. (Box 13, Folder 388)
    - Outline., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 389)
    - Outline., 9 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 389)
    - Lyrics., 14 leaves; various sizes. (Box 13, Folder 390)
      Found in folder marked: Please Return to J.P. Warburg 40 Wall Street.
    - Lyrics., 24 leaves; various sizes. (Box 13, Folder 391)
      Typescript and manuscript in Kay Swift's hand(?) in ink.
    - Miscellaneous notes., 6 p.; various sizes. (Box 13, Folder 392)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in ink and crayon.
  - THE GHOST GOES WEST
    - Proposal., 3 p., 6 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 393)
      With: A few random thoughts (1 p.). Notes (9 p.)
  - GIVE THEM SERVICE / by Curt Bois and Max Hanson; English version by Otis Chatfield-Taylor
    - Script., 32 p. + 38 p. + 26 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 394)
  - HERE'S THE PITCH
    - Proposal., 13 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 395)
    - Notes., 5 p; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 395)
      With: 12 miscellaneous p. of notes.
    - Lyrics., 8 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 396)
  - HUNTER'S MOON / by Marc Connelly; music and lyrics by Kay Swift
    - Script., 121 p.; 26 cm. (Box 13, Folder 397)
      With: Music cues (1 p.). Note to Marc Connelly (1 p.)
  - I KNOW WHAT I LIKE
    - Proposal., 9 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 398)
      With: Insert (1 p.). Budget (2 p.)
  - JACK HORNER'S PIE
    - Proposal., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 399)
      Proposal for show incorporating sketches by Robert Lewis Clark (Hark, Hark, the Clark) and George Oppenheimer (Sarah Was There), with musical numbers by Kay Swift and Ralph Freed.
      Folder in which material was found laid in.
  - JOE AND JOSEPHINE
    - Proposal., 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 400)
  - MANY MOONS
    - Notes., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 401)
  - MARBLE AND BRONZE / by Charles Henderson
    - Script., 14 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 402)
      Based on Esme of Paris by Esme Davis
  - MARGO OF PARIS [THREE-RING CIRCUS]
    - Proposal., 1 p. [incomplete], 2 p.; various sizes. (Box 13, Folder 403)
    - Outline., 8 p., 8 p., 9 p., 28 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 403)
      4 copies.
      With: Cast of characters (2 p.)
  - THE MOST BEAUTIFUL TIME OF THE YEAR
    - Proposal., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 404)
  - NEVER A DULL MOMENT
    - Lyrics., 4 leaves; 22 cm. (Box 13, Folder 405)
      Typescript and manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in pencil and ink.
  - NIGHT VOICES / Charles Henderson
    - Script., 8 p.; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 406)
  - NINE-FIFTEEN REVUE
    - Lyrics., 1 leaf; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 407)
      Typescript, annotations in ink.
  - NOTHING IS TOO LOVELY TO BE TRUE
    - Lyrics., 2 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 408)
      With: notes (1 p.)
  - ONE LITTLE GIRL; by Doris Frankel; music and lyrics by Kay Swift
    - Script., 86 p. in various pagings; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 409)
    - Script (incomplete), 52 p. in various pagings; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 409)
    - Script., 57 p. in various pagings; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 409)
      Found in envelope marked: SCRIPT OF "ONE LITTLE GIRL" BY DORIS FRANKEL (1ST ACT & OUTLINE OF 2d ACT) EARLY SCRIPT. SEE BLUE COPY GIVEN K.S. 9/28/30.
      With: Notes to Hans Spialek (3 p., 2 copies). Camp Fire Girls definition (1 p.). Outline of projected song book (2 p.). Number of bars (17 p.). 10 miscellaneous p. of notes.
    - Lyrics., 27 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 13, Folder 410)
  - PARIS '90
    - Script., 40 p., 40 p. [incomplete]; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 411)
    - Script., 42 p. in various pagings; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 411)
      With: 1 p.
    - Cue sheets., 28 p. in various pagings; various sizes. (Box 14, Folder 412)
      Typescript, annotations in pencil, and red and blue pencil.
      With: Instructions (3 p.). Instrumentation (1 p.). Notes (9 p.). Itinerary (1 p.). Order (1 p.). 4 miscellaneous p. of notes.
    - Lyrics., 29 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 413)
  - A PEACEABLE KINGDOM
    - Notes., 2 p.; 32 cm. (Box 14, Folder 414)
      Manuscript in pencil.
    - Further ideas., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 414)
    - Notes., 5 p.; 16 cm. (Box 14, Folder 414)
      Dated: 7/13/66.
    - Notes., 3 p.; 16 cm. (Box 14, Folder 414)
      Manuscript in ink.
    - Notes., 1 p.; 16 cm. (Box 14, Folder 414)
    - Notes., 2 p.; 32 cm. (Box 14, Folder 414)
    - Notes., 2 p.; various sizes. (Box 14, Folder 414)
      Miscellaneous.
  - PRODUCTION NUMBER IDEAS BY ALFRED STERN
    - Notes., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 415)
  - REACHING FOR THE BRASS RING
    - Lyrics., 7 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 416)
      With: notes (2 p.)
  - SARAH WAS THERE / By George Oppenheimer; Music and lyrics by Kay Swift
    - Proposal., 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 417)
    - Sarah was there., 9 p., 10 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 417)
      Outline, 2 copies.
      With: Suggested opening for "Aunt Sarah's antics." Plans for future Aunt Sarah sketches.
    - Aunt Sarah., 16 p., 16 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 418)
      Script, 2 copies
    - General Pesos and the spy., 11 p., 12 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 419)
    - Happy birthday, Aunt Sarah., 24 p., 30 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 420)
    - It's fun to be a doctor., 11 p., 15 p., 11 p., 12 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 421)
      Script, 4 copies
    - Waterloo for two., 16 p., 16 p. 13 p., 13 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 422)
    - Lyrics., 19 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 423)
  - SLAPSRICK [sic] IS FINE AND DANDY
    - Outline., 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 424)
  - SPRING AGAIN / music by Puccini; arranged by Deems Taylor; lyrics by Kay Swift
    - Script., 237 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 425)
      On cover: "Spring Agian" Louis Vernevil - Miton Shubert - Ezra Stone - etc.
      Dated: Aug 11 1950.
      With: Note. Scenes and musical numbers (2 p.)
    - Lyrics., 28 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 426)
  - UNIDENTIFIED
    - Outline., 10 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 427)
    - Outline., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 428)
    - Outline (incomplete), 5 p. in various pagings; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 429)
      With: note from Hunter Galloway (2 p.)
    - Outline., 4 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 430)
    - Notes., 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 431)
      Dated: Sunday, December 1st (12/1/1979)
    - Script., 7 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 432)
      Opening Act 2 only.
    - Lyrics., 4 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 433)
      Notes for recording laid in.
  - WEDDING DAY IN UTAH / by Kay Swift and George Oppenheimer
    - Outline., 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 434)
  - WHAT IF I SHOULD HAUNT YOU WITH A MINOR STRAIN? [WHEN YOU HEAR THIS MUSIC, REMEMBER ME]
    - Outline, 4 copies, 4 p. (2 copies), 2 p., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 435)
    - Lyrics., 1 leaf; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 436)
  - WORLD OF PETS / by Alfred Stern and Hunter Galloway
    - Outline., 11 p.; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 437)
      With: Unit set (1 p.). Package price (1 p.). Budget (2 p.)
  - MISCELLANEOUS LYRICS
    - Lyrics., 156 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 438)
      Typescript and manuscript in pencil and ink
      With: Song lists (4 p.)
- Writings, Series III; .5' (2 boxes)
  This series consists of fictional and nonfictional writings subdivided into works by Kay Swift and works by others. Subseries A is arranged by title. Subseries B is arranged first by author and then by title. Severely aged or damaged pages have been copied onto acid-free paper.
  - Writings by Kay Swift, III.A
    - April day., 4 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 439)
    - Baseball, the love of my life., 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 440)
      See printed article in Folio, December 1975.
    - Baseball, the love of my life., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 440)
      Incomplete, lacks all before p. 3.
    - Challenge in a major key., 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 441)
      Autobiographical sketch.
    - Another version., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 441)
      On page 1: Final draft, 25/4/74.
      Dated: April 29th,1973.
    - Another version., 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 441)
    - Another version., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 441)
    - Everywhere I roam., 11 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 442)
      At top of page 1: Address by Kay Swift, at Stephen Foster - "Jeanie Auditions White Springs, Florida, February 1966."
      1 page of notes laid in.
    - Another version., 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 442)
    - Fresh woods and pastures new., 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 443)
    - Gershwin and the universal touch, 6 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 444)
      Letter laid in.
    - Good loser., 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 445)
    - Here, today!, 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 446)
    - Another version., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 446)
    - Here's the pitch., 48 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 447)
      Not the proposed musical for television entitled Here's the Pitch by Kay Swift and Alfred Freed (see 13/34)
      1 page of old version laid in [at top: old, not to be used]
    - Liner notes., 14 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 448)
      Notes for "Songs by Ira & George Gershwin," with Joan Morris and William Bolcom on Nonesuch Records (H-71358).
      Note in Kay Swift's hand on "The Man I Love": Liner Notes originally by Kay Swift without anyone else.
      Notes for: The man I love. Fascinating rhythm. How long has this been goin on? My cousin in Milwaukee. Nice work if you can get it. Loved walked in. By Strauss. Just another rhumba. The Lorelei. Someone to watch over me. Isn't it a pity. They all laughed. I'll build a stairway to paradise. Our love is here to stay.
    - Another version., 6 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 448)
      By Kay Swift and Robert Kimball.
      Laid in: Back liner credits (2 p.). Printed back liner.
    - A little western, 11 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 449)
    - Melody lingers on., 4 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 450)
      Address delivered at Stephen Foster Memorial "Jeanie Auditions," in White Springs, Florida on February 13 and 14, 1965.
    - Moth man., 7 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 451)
    - None but the brave., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 452)
    - Nothing happens in August., 13 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      Incomplete, lacks p. 7-9.
      Dated: 9/25/62.
    - Another version., 8 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      Note at top of page 1: Latest combined with Sept. 27th [9/26/62 (crossed out)]
    - Another version., 2 p.; 32 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      Dated: 9/28/62.
    - Another version., 2 p; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      Note at top of page 1: NEW STORY WITH A TWIST.
      Dated: October 8th.
    - Another version., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      At top of page 1: Second version.
      Dated: Oct.10.
    - Another version., 2 p.; various sizes. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      Typescript and manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in ink, annotations in pencil.
      On verso of p. 4: old version.
    - Another version., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
    - Another version., 7 p.; 32 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      At top of page 1: original copy.
    - Another version., 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
    - Further story notes., 1 p.; 32 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
    - Notes., 3 p.; 16 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      Part of note pad.
      Dated: Sept. 18.
    - Further notes for story., 2 p; 32 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      Dated: Sept. 19.
    - Story notes., 2 p.; 32 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      Dated: Sept.20.
    - Additional notes., 12 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      Contents: Sept.28th (2 p.). Oct 8 (2 p.). Oct.22 (2 p.). October 23rd (1 p.). Oct.28 (5 p., lacks p. 1). Nov. 20 (1 p.).
    - Suggestions for opening., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
    - Suggested dialogue., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
    - Notes for our story., 3 p.; 32 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
    - Story notes., 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      Street maps.
    - Story notes., 4 p.; various sizes. (Box 15, Folder 453)
      Manuscript in pencil and ink.
    - Recordings, wild but true., 38 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 454)
      4 p. with dates laid in.
    - "Remembering George Gershwin." (Box 15, Folder 455)
      Saturday Review World (October 9, 1978) pages 18-21.
      Excerpted from Robert Kimball and Alfred E. Simon's The Gershwins.
    - Scary old days., 24 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 456)
      3 dated notes laid in.
    - Seven lives, so far., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 457)
    - Another version., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 457)
    - Statement of Kay Swift in support of H.R. 5921., 4 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 458)
    - Another version., 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 458)
      Typescript, annotations in ink and pencil.
    - Another version., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 458)
      Laid in: House Judiciary Committee. Facts about H.R. 5921. The songwriters' view of the juke box exemption. Statement of Morton Gould.
    - Then welcome each rebuff., 98 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 459)
      On cover: By Kay Swift.
    - Another version., 77 p. + 6 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 459)
      On cover: by Kay Swift and Hunter Galloway.
      Includes outline for ending.
    - Another version., 77 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 460)
    - Another version., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 460)
      Page 1 only.
    - Things I never knew till now about animals., 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 461)
      At top of page 1: Note: This piece was published in the NY Daily Mirror, at the request of Seymour Berkson (?) for one of the columns that acted as summer replacement for Walter Winchell, during the summer of 1944 - KS.
    - Untitled., 7 p. (i.e. 8 p.); 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 462)
    - Untitled., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 463)
      Holograph (photocopy).
      Reminiscences about George Gershwin.
    - Another version., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 463)
    - Untitled., 4 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 464)
    - Untitled., 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 465)
    - Unidentified., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 466)
    - Unidentified., 2 p.; 31 cm. (Box 15, Folder 467)
    - Another version., 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 467)
    - Who could ask for anything more? / by Kay Swift -- New York: Simon and Schuster, 1943., 211 p.; 27 cm. (Box 16, Folder 468)
    - Notebook., 26 cm. (Box 16, Folder 469)
      Miscellaneous notes.
      Dated: 1977-8 1980 and 1985.
    - Miscellaneous., 60 leaves; various sizes. (Box 16, Folder 470)
      Jottings, inserts, lists, notes, and miscellaneous.
  - Writings by Others, III.B
    - Writings by Others, Bradshaw, Jon; 144 p.; 28 cm. (Box 16, Folder 471)
      Incomplete, lacks all before p. 104 and after p. 144.
      Book about Libby Holmen.
    - A Sample from The fundamental things apply., Davis, Sheila; 15 p.; 28 cm. (Box 16, Folder 472)
      Computer printout.
    - What fools immortals be., Donald, Peter; 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 16, Folder 473)
    - A woman's New York., Hughes, Alice; 2 p.: 35 cm. (Box 16, Folder 474)
      Dated: October 1, 1959
    - Gershwin + the Rhapsodie in Blue., Korall, Burt; 13 p.; 28 cm. (Box 16, Folder 475)
    - Death doesn't play fair., Levin, Kay W.; 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 16, Folder 476)
      From unidentified magazine (photocopy)
      Kay Levin is one of Kay Swift and James Warburg's three daughters.
    - Maple madness is hard to control., Levin, Kay W.; 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 16, Folder 476)
      Milwaukee Journal, March 2, 1980 (photocopy)
      Page 2 marked: Just for fun! Kay.
    - The murder of Lidice., Millay, Edna St. Vincent, 1892-1950; 8 p.; 28 cm. (Box 16, Folder 477)
    - Another version., 15 p.; 28 cm. (Box 16, Folder 477)
      Note laid in: Dear Hunter: Have had this for some time-expected you would call. Am leaving tonite for Michigan until Sept. 1-all good things to both you + your wife. Hope to see you there. Larry [on verso: Czechoslovakian proper names.... (annotations in blue ink)].
    - Proposal for course or courses in "The American musical theatre.", Myers, Henry; 25 p. + 1 p.; various sizes. (Box 16, Folder 478)
      Written with Kay Swift.
      Dated: July 27th, 1964.
    - Writings by Others, Peale, Norman Vincent, 1898-1993; 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 16, Folder 479)
      P. 1 marked: PRE-SHOW TEASE.
      Excerpt from The Power of Positive Thinking.
    - David O. Selznick's production no. 103, Penn, William; 93 p.; 35 cm. (Box 16, Folder 480)
      From unidentified journal (photocopy)
      Bibliographical note laid in.
    - Variety., Stern, Alfred; 3 p; 28 cm. (Box 16, Folder 481)
    - Diary., Swift, Gertrude Horton Dorr; 390 p.; 28 cm. (Box 16, Folder 482)
      Typescript, annotations in pencil and attached (p. 230)
      Incomplete, lacks all before p. 201.
      Gertrude Horton Dorr Swift is Kay Swift's grandmother.
    - Christmas., Viggers, Ralph; 3 p; 28 cm. (Box 16, Folder 483)
      On p. 3: From a manuscript by Ralph Viggers, written as a[n (crossed out)] "Stars + Stripes" field reporter, for broadcast over AFRS TEHERAN NETWORK STATIONS, P.G.C., AND RECORDED BY H.G. [Hunter Galloway]
- Correspondence, 1936-1989; Series IV; 1.5' (3 boxes)
  This series consists of personal and professional correspondence to and from Kay Swift. Letters are either typescript or manuscript and include drafts and carbon copies. The majority of correspondence dates from the 1950s onward, although there are some letters from earlier decades. Letters are arranged alphabetically by correspondent, then chronologically. Additional correspondence directly related to theatrical projects is located in Series V under project title. Cross references to the project folders have been included in this series for individual correspondents of particular importance. Severely aged or damaged pages have been copied onto acid-free paper.
  - Aarons, Ruth Hughes, 1957; 4 items. (Box 16, Folder 484)
  - Aborn & Anesi, 1988-1989; 7 items. (Box 16, Folder 484)
  - Ahlert Music Pub., 1961 May 28; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 485)
  - Al, 1960 Jan. 2; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 485)
  - Allenberg, Phil Berg-Bert, 1945-1949; 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 485)
  - Allison, Jane, No date; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 485)
  - American Academy of Dramatic Arts, 1971 Oct. 29; 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 485)
  - American Federation of Musicians, 1962 Sept. 27; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 485)
  - American Guild of Authors and Composers (AGAC), 1958-1980; 33 items. (Box 16, Folder 486)
    See also Songwriters' Protective Association (SPA)
  - American Music Theater Festival, 1988 June 16; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 487)
  - American Play Company, 1950 Oct. 9; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 487)
  - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP), 1957-1988; 34 items. (Box 16, Folder 488)
  - Anderson, Ruth, 1965 Apr. 13; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Andrea, 1958 July 29; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Appleton, F.R., Jr., 1959 June 2; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Associated British Picture Corporation, 1958 Mar. 21; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Atkinson, Brooks, 1960 Mar. 9; 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Aucoin, Lionel, 1987 Apr. 1; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Austin, J.R., 1958 Oct. 31; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - B.F., No date; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Balanchine, George, 1974; 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Barr, Glenn, 1984 Aug. 27; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Beaty, Josephine Powell, 1971 June 18; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Benda, Richard, 1958 May 26; 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Bennett, Robert Russell, 1963; 3 items. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Berkshire Theatre Festival, 1978 July 14; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Beverly Hills Club, 1949 Nov. 21; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Biddle, Nicholas D., 1961-1962; 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Biscuit, 1959 Mar. 12; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Blodget, Alden S., 1954 Feb. 11; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Bolz, Henry H., 1954-1959; 57 items. (Box 16, Folder 490)
  - Bolz, Henry H., 1960-1966; 76 items. (Box 17, Folder 491)
  - Borden Company (Box 17, Folder 491)
    see All About Elsie (19/539)
  - Borge, Victor (Box 17, Folder 491)
    see Weissberger, L. Arnold (4/30/54, 5/10/54, 5/12/54, 5/14/54 and 6/8/54)
  - Bradshaw, Jon, 1980 Sept. 4; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 492)
  - The British Broadcasting Corporation, 1966; 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 492)
  - Broude Brothers, 1957 June 24; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 492)
  - Burrows, Abe (Box 17, Folder 492)
    see Weissberger, L. Arnold (9/29/53, 10/24/53, 1/15/54 and 3/23/59)
  - CBS Masterworks, 1987 June 13; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 492)
    see also Rose, Don (5/5/83)
  - Callis, John L., 1950 Sept. 9; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 492)
  - Camp Fire Girls (Box 17, Folder 492)
    see One Little Girl (21/600)
  - Capitol Records, 1951 Jan. 4; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 492)
  - Carlin, Phillips, 1936 Sept. 2; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 492)
  - Carlsen, John A., 1958-1966; 12 items. (Box 17, Folder 492)
  - Carlyle, Louise (Box 17, Folder 492)
    see Paris '90 (3/4/52)
  - Carpenter, E.N., 1964 June 12; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 493)
  - Century Play Company, 1949 July 21; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 493)
  - Chappell & Co., 1952-1970; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 493)
  - Chappell Piano Co., 1958; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 493)
  - Charles, Dick, 1962 May 31; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 493)
  - Charry, Michael, 1986 July 26; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 493)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1958-1963; 16 items. (Box 17, Folder 494)
  - Chemical Corn Exchange Bank, 1958; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 495)
  - Clairol, 1964 Mar.; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 495)
  - Clark, Bobby, 1948; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 495)
  - Miss Cockton, 1964 June 23; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 495)
    re: copyright search
  - Cole, Toby, No date; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 495)
  - Connelly, Marc, 1958; 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 495)
  - Connors Phil J., 1949 Dec. 15; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 495)
  - Cook, Mrs. Joe, 1959 May 18; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 495)
  - Copland, Aaron, 1981 Feb.; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 495)
  - Cosmopolitan, 1964; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 495)
  - Cotes, Peter, 1958; 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 495)
  - Craeybeckx, M., 1955 Jan. 18; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 496)